









# **Pham Minh Phuc** IT Expert

20/02

Òζ Male

flashphuc219@gmail.com

District 6, Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nam

0906686281

#### **SUMMARY**

♦ I am a passionate about new technologies and can sit for hours in front of my screen to watch how them were made. Punctuality person, plan out before what I'll do or targets were assigned. On my desk, I always have a small calendar in which I can note the date of meeting, deadlines. Hoping with a little experience in the web programming field (front-end) and deployments, I can contribute to the development of the company.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### 07/2020 - 02/2021



# **Cybersoft - Cyberlearn Programing Education Center**

- ♦ Programming course: thinking in programming, problem-solving, Java language, OOP
- ♦ Front-end Foundation course: basic knowledge of HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap 4, SASS/SCSS, Javascript (ES5/ES6), Jquery, AJAX, Git, ...

#### 02/2017 - 06/2017

#### VnPro Center



- ♦ I had knowledge about Networking(LAN, WAN, Wifi...)
- ♦ I was teached and contacted with devices of Cisco (Router, Switch...)

#### 09/2011 - 09/2016

#### **Ton Duc Thang University**

♦ Major: Telecommunication

♦ Total score: 6.51.



#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### 08/2022 - 12/2022

#### FREELANCER IT

- ♦ Troubleshoot about the network, mail, software, hardware by remote support (Anydesk, Ultraviewer, Teamviewer...) or On-site
- ♦ Install the softwares which are asked, active or reinstall Win10.
- ♦ Fix errors about the laptop's driver, sound, camera, monitor...
- ♦ Manage Microsoft Office 365, Microsoft Azure, Onedrive, Print sever, Wifi System, Google Workspace (G Suite)....
- ♦ Replace the parts of laptop or PC (RAM, hard disk, battery...). Familiar with models of HP, Dell, Asus, Acer...

#### 12/2021 - 08/2022

# JOINT STOCK COMPANY TRUONG HAI GROUP



Technical Administrative Specialist(IT Helpdesk)

- ♦ Support users when experiencing problems with computer machinery (Win errors, machines not up, full mail, screen not up ...)
- ♦ Install computer equipment, necessary software (AutoCAD, Itax, HTKK, Nitro ...) for users, manage equipment, arrange and transport
- ♦ Do the paperwork handed over to users, direct events large and small are organized in conjunction with the event department
- ♦ Write a document instructing new personnel to use electronic devices, as well as internal installation
- ♦ Manage printer servers, create accounts for users, join domain, install mail, click network cables ...
- ♦ Creating the documents For new eployees or new softwares, solutions, devices. Setup meeting room (offline or online) for head officers Sometimes I supplied the infrastructure department (clean and Organize server room) Remote the peer's device by damware or ultraviewer for fixing Errors.

## **Alpha Apparel Group Corporation**



Operation Expert(IT Helpdesk)

- ♦ Installation, maintennance, hardware clean. Follow operation system, setup software(Camera, AI, Corel...)
- ♦ Taking the network system are been operated fluently. If system is been taken break-down, will report suppliers to support right now. Suggesting the new configuration's PC or laptop to departments. Contacting the suppliers to supply products and hand over.

8/2019 - 3/2021

## Co.opMart Supermarket



IT Employee

- ♦ Onsite in the Coopmart and support customers and colleagues about the company's software, hardware, server, cash...
- ♦ Fix and update the company's software, hardware, server, cash...

8/2017 - 2/2019

## Dcorp R-Keeper Vietnam - Ho Chi Minh City

Deployment Employee and Command Center



- ♦ Deploy POS software(R-keeper7) for customers: Redsun, Golden Gate, New Pearl...
- ♦ Answer the questions about the software on the hotline. Support and solve by TeamViewer or ultra viewer about the software's bugs. if I solve impossibly, I'll onsite to the customers(with the condition include the customer sign technology contract)

08/2016 - 11/2016

## FPT Shop - Ho Chi Minh City (FRT)



Support Technology And Sale

- ◆ Support Technology for the customer and sell items in the shop.
- ♦ Check products, software, date experience, licenses...
- ♦ Solve customer's incidents (the black screen, the battery is been failed, the speaker is inactive...)

 02/2017 - 06/2017
 ◆ CCNA Certification (Cisco Certified Network Associate) (Vnpro, Ho Chi Minh City)

 03/2016
 ◆ TOEIC 505 (IIG, Ho Chi Minh City)

 SKILSS
 Front-end Developer
 ◆ HTML5/CSS3, JavaScript, Git, React...

 Microsoft Office
 ◆ Word, Excel, Power Point...

 English
 ◆ Communicating (Intermediate), reading documents, writing email

**Soft skills** ♦ Teamwork, self study